http://www.solver.com/privacy

Search
Analyst ToolsProduct OverviewAnalytic Solver for ExcelAnalytic Solver OverviewAnalytic Solver OptimizationAnalytic Solver SimulationAnalytic Solver Data MiningAnalytic Solver BasicRASON Decision ServicesSolver EnginesSolver AcademyDeveloper ToolsProduct OverviewSolver SDK PlatformXLMiner SDK PlatformRASON Decision ServicesSolver EnginesLearnCase StudiesTraining WebinarsData Mining WebinarOptimization WebinarSimulation WebinarSolver TutorialsOptimization TutorialsSimulation TutorialsData Mining TutorialsExcel ExamplesFinance ExamplesInvestment ExamplesProduction ExamplesDistribution ExamplesPurchasing ExamplesScheduling ExamplesVideo DemosSupportTechnical SupportConsulting HelpSolver.AcademyOnline HelpExcel Solver HelpData Mining HelpUser GuidesExcel User GuidesSDK User GuidesRecommended BooksOrderProduct CatalogTypes of LicensesLicense and WarrantyLicense AgreementLimited WarrantyStandard vs Custom TermsInvoicing Payment
Free Trial
Contact UsLogin
Live Chat
Help Desk
Frontline Systems Privacy Policy
You are hereHome
Frontline Systems is committed to protecting your personal information. Our Privacy Policy is designed to protect the information that we collect from you over the web or other means while providing you with our products and services. This Privacy Policy relates to our use of any personal information you provide to us via phone or text, by email, at events, in correspondence, via our websites Solver.com, Rason.com, AnalyticSolver.com, and Solver.Academy, and via our free and paid software products. We want you to understand what information about you does (and does not) become available to us when you communicate with us over the Internet; what we do (and don't do) with this information; and how you can control what happens to your personal information.
Who are we?
Frontline Systems, Inc. is a privately held corporation registered in Nevada, United States with offices in Incline Village, Nevada and Reno, Nevada. If you have any questions about our policies, please contact us at the address, phone, fax, or email below, or use our Contact Page.
Frontline Systems, Inc.Mail:  P.O. Box 4288, Incline Village, NV 89450, USAPhone:  775-831-0300Toll-Free:  888-831-0333 (USA Only)Fax:  775-831-0314Email:  privacy@solver.com
For EU residents:
Frontline Systems has appointed DPR Group as its Data Protection Representative for the purposes of GDPR (the European Union's General Data Protection Regulation). If you are an EU resident (a "data subject") and you have a question, or otherwise want to exercise your rights in respect of personal data, you may contact us directly by submitting this form, or you may contact DPR Group (i) online at DPR's website, (ii) via email to DPR's email address quoting Frontline Systems, Inc. in the subject line, or (iii) via postal mail in your home country, to the appropriate address listed in this document. (Given the speed of postal mail, we encourage you to use the web or email.)
For California residents:
The California Consumer Protection Act (CCPA) doesn't apply to Frontline Systems, because we are below the CCPA's company size (annual revenue) threshold, and because we don't derive ANY revenue from selling personal information. But please read this page to see what we do (not much) with your personal information, and please do contact us with any questions.
Please read the summary below. Follow these links for specific information on various privacy topics:
Web Analytics and Identification Via "Cookies"
Email Addresses, Postal Addresses, and Telephone Numbers
Software Usage Tracking and Active Support
Add-ins for Excel Online and Google Sheets Using RASON®
Other Add-ins for Excel Online and Google Sheets
What information do we collect about you?
When you create an account using the online registration system on any of our websites, sign up for a webinar, or participate in our services or activities, we may receive personal information about you. This typically includes your name, email address, company or university, country and telephone, industry and user type, graduation date for students, and web pages visited. This information enables us to deliver our software and services, and provide the most relevant online content you select.
When you ask for help via live chat, phone or email, our system creates a support ticket that temporarily holds your requests and our responses. When you ask us to review a model (expressed in Excel, RASON® or programming code), the model may contain personal or company information; we always safeguard this information, and on request we can execute a mutual non-disclosure agreement (NDA) for the model.
Our websites also use cookies to enable you (and only you) to login and access your account, download our software Setup programs, user guides, example models and other digital content. Please also note that our websites may include hyperlinks to other websites on the Internet, which have their own privacy practices, and may use their own cookies.
How do we use the information we collect about you?
We use your personal information for "contract performance" purposes including the following:
to deliver our products and services, online/email content, including licenses that enable your use
to provide you with information about how to use our software, services, activities or online/email content
to offer assistance in case you encounter problems/error messages in your use of our software or services
to analyze how our software works with your model, in response to a live chat or technical support request you have made
to analyze and improve the operation of our websites and software for all users (our "legitimate interests")
If we propose to use your personal information in another way, we will notify you first, and give you the opportunity to withhold or withdraw your consent for the use of your personal information for purposes other than those listed above.
When may we contact you?
We may contact you for "contract performance" purposes (including evaluations/free trials):
to provide information about the software, service, activity or online content you have requested
to respond to an inquiry, live chat or technical support request you have made
to inform you of new versions of software or services released after you initially evaluated or purchased a license
to invite you to participate in surveys about products or services you've evaluated or purchased (participation is always voluntary)
What if you are age 16 or younger?
If you are age 16 or younger, please get your parent/guardian's permission before you provide any personal information to us. Without this consent, we cannot accept personal information from you.
How long will we keep your personal information?
When you create an account using the online registration system on any of our websites, we will maintain the personal information you provide until you request to close/delete the account, by contacting us. (We expect to soon offer a "self-service" way to close your account.)
When you request a trial license, purchase or renew a license for our software our services, we will maintain the related personal information until the license expires, and for a 60-day "grace period" thereafter.
Support tickets created when you ask for help via live chat, phone or email are maintained until they are marked "solved" by you or by us. You or we can reopen a ticket for four days after it is "solved"; then it is marked as permanently "closed". All "closed" tickets are archived after 120 days.
In our accounting system, we will maintain only the required information in transaction records (such as quote, orders, invoices and payments) for as long as we are required to do so for financial and tax reporting purposes.
Can you find out what personal information we hold about you?
Yes – you can view, edit and remove much of the information we hold about you by simply logging into your account on Solver.com, clicking the "Account" link in the upper right, then clicking the "Edit" tab on the user account page. You can request a copy of all the personal information we hold about you, and have any inaccuracies corrected, when you contact us as shown at the top of this page. We may require you to prove your identity with government-issued identification. We will use diligent efforts to supply, correct or delete personal information about you in our various systems (including archived support tickets if requested).
Will we share your personal information with anyone else?
We will keep your information confidential within our company. We do not sell or share your information with anyone else, except where disclosure is required by law (for example to government and law enforcement agencies). We use certain third party vendors to process your information on our behalf; these vendors are obligated to keep your information confidential and not to share it with anyone else.
We use Transport Layer Security (TLS) – formerly known as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) and shown by the https: prefix – to encrypt all data transferred between your browser and any of our websites, and for communication between sites. We also use encryption for data stored on our cloud servers, and use a numeric identifier in lieu of your name or email wherever possible ("pseudonymisation"). We use a third party, Level 1 PCI (Payment Card Industry) compliant vendor for all credit card data; we do not "see" or handle any of your credit card data within our company.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time, so you may wish to check it each time you submit personal information to us. The date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page. If you do not agree to these changes, please do not continue to use our websites or submit personal information to us.
We're Here to Help
Question or Comment
Support Live Chat
Consulting Help
Support KnowledgeBase
Call Us
Inside USA: 888-831-0333
Outside: 01+775-831-0300
